http://www.iniche.com/privacy.php

Privacy Policy
Networking Protocol Software for Embedded Processors
Click Here to Contact Us via Email.
PPP, PPPoE
Embedded Security SSL, IPSec, etc.
Network Applications and Device Management Protocols
Web Server (http:// and https://)
Web Client (http:// and https://)
ESMTP - Sending Email
SNMP v1, v2c, v3 and MIB Compiler
DHCPv6
SNTP - Time Synchronization
MQTT / IoT (Client)
Multicast (IGMP and MLD)
Compiler Support
USB (Host)
USB (Device)
Demos & Other FormatsPre-Compiled Libs, Free Demos
Pre-Compiled Protocol Libraries, Free Demos.
Free Time-Limited Demos
iNiche.com Privacy PolicyThe following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the InterNiche website and other online marketing initiatives.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to save any password entered so you don't have to re-enter it each time you revisit the same site areas. A cookie is a small piece of information that is written to and read from your hard drive by your browser at the request of our Web pages. Information stored in cookies is not accessible to Web pages from other websites. Cookies themselves cannot retrieve any information about you or your computer's configuration. Other than the small amount of disk space used to store a cookie, they are harmless.
Registration forms on the site may require you to give us contact information (such as name, mailing address and email address). We may use contact information from the registration forms to send you information about our company. Your contact information is also used to follow up with additional mail or email communication when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving any such future mailings.
This site contains links to other sites. InterNiche is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such linked websites.
InterNiche uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this statement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. By using this site, you authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private.
Disclaimer
InterNiche may have patents or pending patent applications, trademarks, copyrights, or other intellectual property rights covering subject matter on this site. The furnishing of the content on this site does not give you any license to the patents, trademarks, copyrights, or other intellectual property rights, except as expressly provided in any written license agreement from InterNiche.
InterNiche does not warrant that the quality or performance of any software distributed through this site, including any Partner software, (collectively, the "software") will meet any specific end user requirements (including compatibility) or that such end user will be able to achieve any particular results from use of the software or that the software will operate free from error. INTERNICHE DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED AND STATUTORY INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY INTERNICHE, ITS DEALERS, DISTRIBUTORS, AGENTS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL IN ANY WAY INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THIS WARRANTY.
Trademark Information
InterNiche, NicheStack and the InterNiche logo are trademarks of InterNiche Technologies, Inc. The trademarks, logos and service marks ("Marks") displayed on this Web site are the property of InterNiche or other third parties. You are not permitted to use the Marks without the prior written consent of InterNiche or such third party which may own the Marks. Other product and company names mentioned herein may be the trademarks of their respective owners.
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
Contacting the Website Administrator
Please direct all questions concerning the foregoing or other website content to:
InterNiche Technologies, Inc.
About InterNiche
Partial Customer List
Partners
Working at InterNiche
For More Info ...
Free Downloads
Time-Limited Demos
Site Map
Copyright © InterNiche Technologies, Inc.2005-2016 All rights reserved.
Contact iNiche
Privacy Policy
InterNiche software is now part of HCC Embedded.
This site is no longer updated and may contain out of date information
Click here to go to HCC for latest information.
Click here to accept cookies and continue browsing InterNiche website.
Click here to read the complete Interniche Documentation
